[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This dish is usually cooked in a large, flat pan. It is most typical for the region of Valencia, Spain and contains ingredients such as rice, saffron and olive oil.", "correct_answer": "Paella", "incorrect_answers": ["Enchilada", "Lasagna", "Tajine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these sea mammals is not in the endangered species lists?", "correct_answer": "Pilot whale", "incorrect_answers": ["Fin Whale", "Blue Whale", "Humpback Whale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1982 Julie Andrews, James Garner and Lesley Ann Warren starred in this musical about a female impersonator.", "correct_answer": "Victor Victoria", "incorrect_answers": ["Bosum Buddies", "Mrs. Doubtfire", "Mr. Mom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of these movies does Jennifer Anistons character fall in love with her gay best friend?", "correct_answer": "The Object of My Affection", "incorrect_answers": ["Along Came Polly", "Friends with Money", "The Good Girl"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What company introduced the Radarange, the first countertop home microwave oven, in 1967?", "correct_answer": "Amana", "incorrect_answers": ["Kennmore", "GE", "Tappan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Studies of raccoons intelligence have shown that raccoons are capable of performing this activity.", "correct_answer": "Opening locks", "incorrect_answers": ["Understanding spoken words", "Painting", "Differentiating sounds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Grammy award-winning singer and songwriter played the role of Samuel Ramos in the 2004 action movie Man on Fire?", "correct_answer": "Marc Anthony", "incorrect_answers": ["Enrique Iglesias", "Chayanne", "Ricky Martin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On October 24, 1901, Annie Edson Taylor became the first person to go over the Niagara Falls in a barrel as a publicity stunt. How old was she at the time?", "correct_answer": "63", "incorrect_answers": ["23", "43", "33"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This word means fear of cats. Meow!", "correct_answer": "Ailurophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Arachnephobia", "Alektorophobia", "Apiphobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which comic book publisher did King Kong and Godzilla share?", "correct_answer": "Dark Horse", "incorrect_answers": ["DC", "Manga", "Marvel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Blue pages are a telephone directory of these.", "correct_answer": "Government offices", "incorrect_answers": ["Business offices", "Celebrities home numbers", "Brothels numbers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrayed agent 007 in the seventeenth James Bond movie GoldenEye in 1995?", "correct_answer": "Pierce Brosnan", "incorrect_answers": ["Daniel Craig", "Sean Bean", "Timothy Dalton"]}]